爸爸要我们继承他的遗志
Dad wants us to pick up where he left off.
救助他人 猎杀恶魔 家族事业
Saving people, hunting things, the family business.
你想把那个魔鬼引到这里 对吧？想演一场滑稽戏吗？
You plan on bringing the demon here.Having some stupid, macho showdown.
- 我是有计划的 - 迪恩快死了 而你却在这计划
- I have a plan, Sam. - Dean is dying and you have a plan.
在确定迪恩没事前 我是不会追捕那个魔鬼的
I won't hunt this demon.Not until we know Dean's okay.
你真以为能困的住我吗？
Did you really think you could trap me?
哦 我才不想困住你 只是想和你做个交易
I don't wanna trap you.I wanna make a deal.
我会把柯尔特和子弹给你 但你得答应帮助迪恩
I will give you the Colt and the bullet.But you gotta help Dean.
- 让他起死回生 - 你还得加大你的注码
- You gotta bring him back. - You still need to sweeten the pot.
- 所罗门之印 - 这个防御圈真的能起作用吗？
- Key of Solomon. - Protective circles really work?
魔鬼进去后就会被困住 失去力量
Get a demon in one, they're trapped, powerless.
- 怎么回事？- 喔 上帝啊
- What's going on? - Oh, my God.
快去叫医生
Get a doctor.
快去
Run.
- 发生什么事了？告诉我 - 狗
- What happened?Talk to me. - Dogs.
- 你别死 宝贝 - 狗 黑狗
- Stay with us, baby. - Dogs.Black dogs.
鲍勃？罗伯特 别丢下我一个人
Bob?Robert, don't you die on me.
[邪恶力量 第2季第8集]
很好 谢谢 菲尔
Great.Thanks, Phil.
我们的负面消息真多啊
So much for our low profile.
你在圣路易斯还被抓过
You got a warrant in St.Louis.
现在你又正式进入联邦调查局的数据库里了
You're officially in the Feds' database.
- 伙计 这么说我出名了 - 迪恩 这可不好笑
- I'm like Dillinger or something. - Dean It's not funny.
这样我们就更难做事了 我们要小心行事了
Makes it harder, we gotta be careful.
那他们怎么说你来着？
What do they got on you?
我想他们还没有登出来
I'm sure they just haven't posted it yet.
- 没有同谋罪 什么都没有？- 闭嘴
- No accessory?Nothing? - Shut up.
- 你在妒忌 - 我才没有
- You're jealous. - No, I'm not.
好吧 关于那件案子 你查到了些什么？
All right, what do you got on the case there...
无辜无害的年轻人
you innocent, harmless young man, you?
建筑师肖恩·博伊登 从自家的房顶上掉下来
"Architect Sean Boyden plummeted to his death from the roof of his home...
而且是自己设计的公寓
a condominium he designed."
自己造个高楼 然后从上面跳下来 真是经典
Build a high-rise and jump off the top of it.Classy.
- 他们什么时候打电话给动物控制中心的？- 二天前
- When did he call Animal Control? - Two days earlier.
- 他真有提到过"黑狗"的事？- 是的
- Did he actually say, black dog? - Yeah.
凶狠野蛮的黑狗
"Vicious, wild black dog."
警方找不到的 而且其他人也没见过
The authorities couldn't find it, no one else saw it.
事实上警方都觉得有些困惑
In fact, authorities are confused...
野狗是如何避开看门人
as to how a wild dog could get past the doorman...
并乘电梯上楼 然后城里最好的建筑里闲庭慢步
take the elevator and roam the halls of the cushiest joint in town.
那之后也没来过电话
After that, no more calls...
也没来上过班 两天后 他就消失了
he doesn't show up for work.Two days later he takes a swan dive.
- 我们是不是真的和黑狗干上了？- 有可能
- We're dealing with an actual black dog? - Well, maybe.
- 那这事有什么传说？- 都是一些传言
- What's the lore on it? - It's vague.
黑狗存在于世界的每个角落里
There are spectral black dogs all over the world.
有人说那是动物的灵魂 也有人说是亡灵
Some say they're animal spirits, others, death omens.
不管是什么 他们肯定是那种大而凶猛的家伙
But anyways, whatever they are, they're big, nasty
他们能把你的脚撕成碎片
I bet they could hump the crap out of your leg.Look at that one.
什么？他们真的会的
What?They could.
那作为肖恩·博伊登的生意伙伴
So you and Sean Boyden were business partners...
你们已经共事十年了？
for almost 10 years, right?
是的 再问一次 你们这次来是…
That's right.One more time, this is for?
为了了解富有才华的博伊登先生 《建筑摘要杂志》
A tribute for Mr.Boyden.Architectural Digest.
- 觉得可笑吗？- 没有
- Funny to you? - No.
只是"才华"这词 是的
It's just a Tribute.Yeah.
肖恩一直很有才华
See, Sean always got the tributes.
他虽然抛开的家庭
He kills himself...
选择自杀这条路
leaves me and his family behind...
- 但还是得到了另一种才华 - 是的
- ...but he gets another tribute. - Right.
知道他为什么要自杀吗？
Any idea why he'd do such a thing?
不知道 他生活的很不错
I have no clue.I mean, he lived the charmed life.
- 怎么个不错法？- 他是个天才
- How so? - He was a flat out genius.
我已经算能干的了 但和他相比 嗯…
I mean, I'm capable, but next to him...
我是永远达不到他那种程度的
It wasn't always that way, either.
达不到吗？
No?
想知道真相吗？
Wanna know the truth?
以前他连狗窝都做来出来
There was a time when he couldn't design a pup tent.
十年前 他在一个叫Lloyd的酒吧做调酒师
Hell, 10 years ago, he worked as a bartender...
也不是什么高级酒吧
at this place called Lloyd's.Complete dive.
- 那他怎么变了？- 你问倒我了
- Right.So, what changed? - You got me.
但一夜之间他就有这样的天份了
But overnight, he gets this huge commission...
并开始设计东西
and he starts designing...
开始设计一些从没见过的
He starts designing the most ingenious buildings...
天才之作
anyone has ever seen.
感觉他就像凡高和莫扎特一样 只是…
It was like the level of Van Gogh and Mozart
- 什么？- 真是有趣…
- What? - It's funny.
天才们… 总是英年早逝 不是吗？
True geniuses, they seem to die young, don't they?
拥有这样的天分
To have that kind of talent.
为什么…
Why ?
为什么就这样走了？
Why just throw it away?
- 怎么样？- 那个秘书的名字叫 卡莉
- So? - The secretary's name is Carly.
23岁 她喜欢皮艇…
She's 23, she kayaks...
而且它们真的存在
and they're real.
你都没问她有关黑狗的事 不是吗？
You didn't ask if she's seen any black dogs lately?
这星期的所有投诉电话 任何有关大的
Every complaint called in this week about anything big
黑的 或狗样的动物
black or dog like.
一共有19通
There's 19 calls in all.
和…
And...
我不知道这是什么
I don't know what this thing is.
- 卡莉的个人空间？- 个人空间 那是什么东西？
- You mean Carly's MySpace address? - MySpace, what the hell is that?
说真的 是不是什么黄色网站？
Seriously, is that like some sort of porn site?
我发誓 如果再有野狗在隔壁叫的话…
I swear, if this is another Pomeranian barking in the neighbor's yard...
下午好女士
Afternoon, madam.
动物控制中心
Animal Control.
- 昨天已经有人来过了 - 我们是跟进这事的
- Someone already came yesterday. - Oh, we're just following up.
我们在找希尔维亚·帕尔曼医生
We're looking for a Dr.Sylvia Pearlman.
医生 她…
The doctor, well, she
我不知道她什么时候能回来 她已经出去二天了
I don't know when she'll be back.She left two days ago.
那你是？
Okay.And you are?
- 我是她的女佣 - 那医生去哪了？
- I'm Ms.Pearlman's maid. - Where did the doctor go?
我也不知道 她打好包就走了 也没说去哪
I'm not sure.She just packed and went.She didn't say where.
- 那个走失的狗 你们后来找到了吗？- 还没
- That stray dog, did you find it finally? - Not yet.
你没有亲眼看见那狗 是吗？
You know, you didn't ever happen to see the dog yourself, did you?
是的 我连狗叫声都没听过
Well, no.I never even heard it.
我都开始怀疑是不是医生自己想像出来的
I was starting to think the doctor was imagining it.
- 但她不是那种会瞎想的人 所以… - 当我看到她是
- She's not like that.So - I read she was...
外科主任医师时
a chief surgeon at the hospital?
我还以为她有42 43岁吧
She's gotta be what, 42, 43?
- 但是这么年轻就能坐上这个职位 - 历史上最年轻的一位
- That's pretty young for that job. - Youngest in the history.
她在十年前就升到现在的职位了
She got the position 10 years ago.
- 一夜成功 10年之前 - 是的 我们也认识一位这样的人
- An overnight success, 10 years ago. - Yeah, we know a guy like that.
看这个
Oh, look at this.
Lloyd酒吧
Lloyd's Bar.
帕尔曼小姐？
Miss Pearlman?
我已经给你打了几小时电话了
I've been calling for hours.
你要么走人 要么付今晚的房租
You need to vacate the room or you gotta pay for another night.
好的 没问题
Okay.No problem.
- 嘿 - 什么？
- Hey. - Yeah?
- 有点奇怪 - 怎么了？
- That's weird.What?
有人故意种的？
You think someone planted these?
- 种在这些杂草里？- 这个 这叫什么来着？
- In the middle of all these weeds? - These are, what do you call them?
- 欧蓍花？- 是的
- Yarrow flowers. - Yeah.
- 是不是用在一种仪式上的？- 是的 一种召唤仪式
- Used for certain rituals, aren't they? - Yeah, actually, summoning rituals.
10年前两个人一夜成功
So two people become sudden successes about 10 years ago...
而且同时都在Lloyd酒吧出现过
around the time they were here at Lloyd's.
碰巧都是在同一个十字路口 你觉得呢？
Where there happens to be a crossroads.You think?
让我们来查查吧
Let's find out.
觉得像死亡中心吗？
This seem about the dead center to you?
找到了
Yahtzee.
我打赌里面是墓地土
I'd be willing to bet that's graveyard dirt.
一块黑猫的骨头
And a black cat bone.
真的有这样的做法 是南方内陆伏都教的方法
That's serious spell work.I mean, that's deep south hoodoo stuff.
用来召唤魔鬼的
Used to summon a demon.
而且不只召唤一个
Not just summon one.
在十字路口召唤总是很灵验
Crossroads are where pacts are made.
这些人肯定是和魔鬼做了交易
These people are actually making deals with the damn thing.
让他们有好日子过
You know, because that always ends good.
他们看见了狗
They're seeing dogs, all right.
但不是黑狗 他们看见了地狱捕手
But not black dogs, they are seeing hellhounds.
魔鬼的爪牙
Demonic pit bulls.
不管是什么魔鬼 他们会回来而且取人性命
And whoever this demon is, it's back and it's collecting.
还有那个女医生 不管她逃到哪里
That doctor lady, wherever she's running...
都是逃不掉的
she aingt running fast enough.
上帝. -. -
Holy
上帝？
Holy?
再猜猜
Guess again.
我想弹吉它
I wanna play guitar.
我想你让我成为 这世上最好的蓝调演奏家
I want you to make me the best bluesman ever lived.
如果那是你想要的
If that's what you want.
那我们要…
So how do we ?
我们要握手吗？
Do we shake on it?
就像罗伯特·约翰逊的传说一样吗？
So it's just like the Robert Johnson legend, right?
在这十字路口 用你的灵魂来做交易？
Selling your soul at the crossroads kind of deal?
他并不是什么传奇 你知道他的音乐
Yeah, except that wasn't a legend.You know his music.
你不知道罗伯特·约翰逊的歌？
You don't know Robert Johnson's songs?
萨姆 他的歌词里面都是线索
There's occult references all over his lyrics.I mean:
《十字路口》？《我和恶魔》？
"Cross Road Blues", "Me and the Devil Blues"...
《我身后的魔爪》？
"Hell Hound on My Trail"?
传说他是被自己的血给呛死的
The story goes that he died choking on his own blood.
说他产生了幻觉并喃喃自语 并提到恶狗的事
He was hallucinating and muttering about big, evil dogs.
- 现在历史又重演了 - 是的
- Now it's happening all over again. - Yeah.
我们要查出还有谁作了交易
We gotta find out if anyone else struck any bargains here.
是啊 我们要帮这些人善后吗？
Great.So we gotta clean up people's mess for them?
这些人自己也不干净
They're not exactly squeaky clean.
没人用枪指着他们的头 逼他们和恶魔做交易的
Nobody forced them to play Let's Make a Deal.
- 那我们就要看着他们死？- 有人自己在找死
- So, what?We just leave them? - Someone goes over Niagara in a barrel...
- 你就要跳出来营救他们？- 迪恩…
- ...you gonna try to save them? - Dean.
那好. -. -那好吧
All right.Fine.
在这样仪式中 你要把自己的照片过进去 是吧？
Rituals like this, you put your own photo into the mix, right?
那这个人也许也做了交易 查查有没有谁认识他…
This guy probably summoned the thing.I'll go see if anyone inside knows him.
如果他还活着的话
If he's still alive.
- 这人叫什么？- 乔治·达罗
- What's the guy's name again? - George Darrow.
很明显也经常去Lloyd酒吧
Apparently quite the regular at Lloyd's.
这地方并没有那么好 是吧？
His house probably aingt up next on MTV Cribs, is it?
是的 那他到底做了什么交易 他不是…
Yeah.So, whatever kind of deal he made...
肯定不是为了钱
It wasn't for cash.
天知道？可能他屋子里都是穿着比基尼的美女呢
Oh, who knows?Maybe his place is full of babes in Princess Leia bikinis?
我只是说说 这家伙手头拿的可是张巨额支票啊
I'm just saying, this guy's got one epic bill come due.
希望他至少换的是有趣的东西
Hope at least he asked for something fun.
看看那个
Look at that.
这是什么 胡椒吗？
What is that, pepper?
- 你们是谁？- 是乔治·达罗？
- Who the hell are you? - George Darrow?
我不会买东西的
I'm not buying anything.
我想你是用错东西了
Looks like you went for the wrong shaker.
如果你不想让恶魔靠近 你应该用盐
Usually when you wanna keep something evil out, you go for the salt.
- 我不知道你们在说什么 - 说的是这个
- I don't know what you're talking about. - Talking about this.
告诉我… 你见过那些地狱猎犬了吗？
Tell me.You seen that hellhound yet?
听着 我们想帮你
Look, we wanna help.
求你了 5分钟就好
Please.Just five minutes.
- 外面的那些是什么东西？- 死人粉
- So, what is that stuff out front? - Goofer dust.
什么 你们自认什么都知道 却不知道死人粉
You boys think you know something about something but not goofer dust?
我们对什么都知道一点
We know a little about a lot of things.
足够让我们武装起来就好了
Just enough to make us dangerous.
- 这是什么？- 伏都
- What is it? - Hoodoo.
我祖母告诉我的
My grandma taught me.
这样可以防住魔鬼
Keeps out demons.
我们知道魔鬼的
Demons we know.
那拿着它吧
Well, then, keep it.
也许对你们会有帮助
Maybe it'll do you some good.
只剩4分钟了
Four minutes left.
达罗先生
Mr.Darrow.
- 我们知道你有麻烦 - 是的 是你自找的
- We know you're in trouble. - Yeah, that you got yourself into.
但并不是无法挽回 不是吗？
But it's not hopeless, all right?
- 肯定有我们能做到的办法的 - 听着
- There's gotta be something we can do. - Listen.
我知道你们想要帮忙
I get that you boys wanna help.
但有时候一个人自己做的事 就要自己来承担结果
But sometimes a person makes their bed and they just got to lie down in it.
是我召唤那魔鬼在先的
I'm the one who called that demon in the first place.
- 你向那个魔鬼要了什么？- 那时我很失败
- What did you do it for? - I was weak.
谁不想过好一点？
I mean, who don't wanna be great?
谁不想活得有意义？
Who don't want their life to mean something?
我只是…
I just
我只是没有想到要付出那么大的代价
I just never thought about the price.
- 你觉得值得吗？- 当然不值
- Was it worth it? - Hell, no.
我向他换取天分
Of course, I asked for talent.
我早该成名了
Should have gone for fame.
但我还是一无名小卒
I'm still broke.
而且孤独
And lonely.
只剩下这一堆没人要的画
Just now I got this pile of paintings don't nobody want.
这并不是最坏的
But that wasn't the worst.
继续说
Go on.
魔鬼从没离开过
Demon didn't leave.
虽然我也没有指望它离开
I never counted on that.After our deal was done...
在跟我签订了契约之后 那家伙在Lloyd酒吧呆了一周
the damn thing stayed at Lloyd's for a week...
跟人聊天 还签了更多的契约
just chatting, making more deals.
我试图警告人们 但谁会听一个老酒鬼的话？
I tried to warn folks, but who's gonna listen to an old drunk?
- 还有多少人签了契约？- 有个建筑师 还有个女医生
- How many others are there? - This architect, a doctor lady.
我一直注意着他们 但他们的讣告已经出现上报了
I kept up with them.They been in the papers.
至少他们都成名了
At least they got famous.
还有谁 乔治？拜托 再想想
Who else, George?Come on, think.
噢 还有一个
One more.
嗯 也是个好人
Nice guy too.
哈德森 我想是叫埃文
Hudson.Evan, I think.
我不知道他要的什么
I don't know what he asked for.
现在都无所谓了
Don't matter now.
我们都要受罚了
We done for.
不 不
No.
- 一定有办法解决的 - 你没明白我的话
- There's gotta be a way. - You don't get it.
我才不想逃避
I don't want a way.
- 其实 你并不想… - 那东西是我召唤的
- Look, you don't have - Look, I called that thing.
我自作自受
I brought it on myself.
还连累了别人
I brought it on them.
无论如何 我都会下地狱
I'm going to hell, one way or another.
现在我只想完成最后一幅作品
All I want is to finish my last painting.
一两天就能完成
A day or two, I'm done.
我只想在那之前拖住他
I'm just trying to hold him off till the end.
拖延一段时间
Buy a little time.
小伙子们 走吧 去帮助那些需要帮助的人吧
Okay, boys.Time you went.Go help somebody that wants help.
- 我们不能… - 出去
- We can't just - Get out!
我还要工作呢
I got work to do.
你并不是真的一心求死
You don't really wanna die.
我不是吗？
I don't?
我
I'm...
已经累了
I'm tired.
埃文？你在偷窥你的邻居？
Evan, you're spying on the neighbors?
没 我 好像听到院子里有什么东西 不过什么都没有
No, I-I thought I heard something in the yard, but it's nothing.
- 你都准备好了？- 你知道 如果不是那么了解你的话
- You all ready to go? - If I didn't know better...
我还以为你要赶我走呢
I'd say that you want me out of the house.
当然不是
Of course not.
只是 你… 自从你姐姐生了孩子以后 你就很少去看望她
It's just you've barely seen your sister since she had the baby.
那你周末打算干什么呢？
Well, what are you gonna do all weekend?
呃 没什么 我有些账单要付
Not much, I got some bills to pay.
过来
Come here.
- 我会想你的 - 最好如此
- I'll miss you. - You better.
你知道我爱你 对吧？
You know I love you, right?
直到永远
Forever.
当然了 埃文你还好吗？
Of course.Evan, are you okay?
是的
Yeah.
是的 我很好
Yeah, I'm fine.
现在出发吧
Now get going.
好 我到了以后给你打电话
Okay, I'll call you when I get there.
亲爱的？
Hey, sweetie?
我也爱你
I love you too.
- 你们是？- 你是埃文·哈德森？
- Yes? - Evan Hudson?
- 是的 - 你去过一个叫Lloyd的酒吧吗？
- Yeah. - You ever been to a bar called Lloyd's?
应该是在大约10年以前
Would have been about 10 years ago?
别这样 我们又不是魔鬼
Come on, we're not demons.
还有别的好点子吗？
Any other bright ideas?
等等
Wait.
- 埃文？- 求求你
- Evan? - Please.
- 别伤害我 - 我们不会伤害你的 好吗？
- Don't hurt me. - We're not gonna hurt you.
- 我们是来帮助你的 - 我们对你那个交易一清二楚
- We're here to help you. - We know all about the deal you made.
- 什么？怎么会？- 这不重要
- What?How? - It doesn't matter.
重要的是我们是来阻止它的
We're trying to stop it.
我怎么知道你们不是在骗我？
How do I know you're not lying?
你是不知道 不过你也没有别的选择
Well, you don't, but you're low on options there, buddy boy.
- 你们能阻止它吗？- 不知道 但我们会尽力的
- Can you stop it? - Don't know.We'll try.
- 我不想死 - 现在你当然不想死
- I don't wanna die. - Of course you don't.Not now.
迪恩 别说了
Dean.Stop.
你许了什么愿 嗯？
What did you ask for, anyway, Ev?
永远不生病 打牌百战百胜 还是别的什么？
Never need Viagra?Bowl a perfect game?What?
我妻子
My wife.
没错 一个姑娘 什么能比这更好呢
Right.Getting the girl.That's worth a trip to hell.
- 迪恩 闭嘴 - 不
- Dean.Stop. - No.
他是对的 我做了交易
He's right.I made the deal.
没有人强迫我
Nobody twisted my arm.
那个女人 不管她是什么东西 她在那个酒吧里
That woman, or whatever she was, at the bar
说能实现我的任何愿望 开始我以为她是个疯子 但…
She said I could have anything I wanted.I thought she was nuts at first, but
我不知道
I don't know, I was...
我… 我那时候很绝望
I was desperate.
绝望？
Desperate?
朱莉快死了
Julie was dying.
你是为了救她？
You did it to save her?
她得了癌症 医生停止了治疗 把她送到收容所
She had cancer.They stopped treatment, they were moving her into hospice.
他们说
They kept saying:
只是时间问题
"A matter of days."
所以 是的 我做了那个交易
So, yeah, I made the deal.
我不后悔
And I'd do it again.
我愿意为她而死
I'd have died for her on the spot.
- 你做这些的时候想过你妻子吗？- 我是为了她这么做的
- Did you think about her in all this? - I did this for her.
你确定？
You sure about that?
我看你是为了自己
I think you did it for yourself.
这样你就不用忍受没有她的生活了
So you wouldn't have to live without her.
但是 现在怎么样？她得忍受没有你的日子了
But guess what, she's gonna have to live without you now.
要是她知道了代价是什么会怎么样？
And what if she knew how much it cost?
要是她知道那是用你的灵魂交换来的？
What if she knew it cost your soul?
你觉得她会是什么感受？
How do you think she'd feel?
好了 够了 埃文
Okay.That's enough.Evan.
别走开 好吗？我们会想到办法的
Sit tight.All right?We're gonna figure this out.
- 你还好吧？- 为什么不好？
- You all right? - Why wouldn't I be?
嘿 我有主意了
Hey, I got an idea.
你用乔治的巫术阻止地狱猎犬
Throw the hoodoo at the hellhound.
别让它靠近埃文 时间越久越好
Keep it away as long as you can.
我要去那个十字路口召唤那个魔鬼
I'll go to the crossroads, summon the demon.
召唤… 你疯了？
Summon Are you nuts?
也许有一点儿
Maybe a little.
不过我可以设个陷阱困住她 我可以驱除她
But I can trap it.I can exorcise it...
或者拖延时间 直到我们找到一劳永逸的解决办法
and buy us time to figure out something.
- 要多长时间？- 一会儿吧
- How much time? - A while.
那些怪物没那么容易 从地狱爬到阳光底下的
It's not easy for them to claw from hell into the sunshine.
- 不行 没门儿 - 不许说不 萨姆
- No.No way. - Not allowed to say no.
- 除非你有别的更好的法子 - 迪恩就别想了好吗？
- Unless you got a better idea. - Forget it.
- 我不会让你召唤那个魔鬼的 - 为什么？
- I'm not letting you. - Why not?
- 因为我不喜欢你的想法 - 你说什么呢？
- I don't like where your head is at. - What?
自从我们发现那个十字路口以后 你就变得急躁了
You've been on edge since we found that crossroads.
- 迪恩 我知道为什么 - 我们没空说这个
- I know why. - Don't have time for it.
是爸爸
Dad.
你觉得爸爸也许也和魔鬼 做了这种交易 对不对？
You think maybe dad made one of these deals, huh?
见鬼 我一直这么想
Hell, I've been thinking it.
我敢肯定你也是的
I'm sure you've been thinking it too.
一切都对得上 对吧？
It fits, doesn't it?
我活着 爸爸死了 那个黄眼睛的魔鬼也有份
I'm alive, dad's dead.Yellow eyed demon was involved.
也许他真这么做了
What if he did?
也许他和魔鬼做了交易
What if he struck a deal?
用他的灵魂换了我的命
My life for his soul?
嘿 我想我听到它了 就在外面
I think I hear it.It's outside.
想办法保护好他 好吗？
Just keep him alive, okay?
- 迪恩？- 快去
- Dean - Go.
那么 到底是什么 让你这样的帅哥来到这种地方呢？
So, what brings a guy like you to a place like this?
- 你召唤了我 - 我很高兴(巫术)起作用了
- You called me? - I'm just glad it worked.
第一次？
First time?
可以这么说
You could say that.
哦 好了 别太低估自己了
Oh, come on, now, don't sell yourself short.
我知道你的一切 迪恩·温彻斯特
I know all about you, Dean Winchester.
- 那么你知道我是谁 - 我读过内部刊物
- So you know who I am? - I get the newsletter.
好吧 别让卖关子了
Well, don't keep me in suspense.
你都听说些什么了？
What have you heard?
好吧 我听说你很英俊
Well, I heard you were handsome...
而且可口
but you're just edible.
我能帮你什么呢 迪恩？
What can I do for you, Dean?
也许我们应该去我的车里
Maybe we should do this in my car.
- 又舒适又隐蔽 - 听起来不错
- Nice and private. - Sounds good to me.
- 这是什么东西？- 死人粉
- What is that stuff? - Goofer dust.
- 你说真的？- 是啊 恐怕是
- You serious? - Yeah.Afraid so.
听着 信不信随你
Look, believe me, don't believe me.Whatever you want.
只是不管怎么样 千万别走出这个圈子 好吗？
Just whatever you do, stay inside this circle, all right?
- 希望我们能做个交易 - 我就是专门干这个的
- So I was hoping we could strike a deal. - That's what I do.
我要你和埃文·哈德森解除契约
I want Evan Hudson released from his contract.
抱歉亲爱的
So sorry, darling.
那个没得商量
That's not negotiable.
- 我会出个好价钱的 - 真的吗？
- I'll make it worth your while. - Oh, really?
- 你用什么交换？- 我自己
- What are you offering? - Me.
噢 噢 噢
Well, well, well.
你要为了别人牺牲自己的生命
You'd sacrifice your life for someone else's?
有其父必有其子啊
Like father, like son.
这是最后的了
That's the last of it.
你知道你爸爸的那个交易 对吧？
You did know about your dad's deal, right?
一命换一命
His life for yours?
哦 虽然不是我和他做的交易 但我真希望是
Now, I didn't make the deal myself, but, boy, I wish I had.
- 请吧 - 真是位绅士
- After you. - Such a gentleman.
魔鬼陷阱？你不是在开玩笑吧？
A devil's trap?You've got to be kidding me.
- 怎么了？- 你听见了吗？
- What? - You hear that?
没有 在哪儿？
No.Where?
就在门外
Right outside the door.
千万别动 好吗？就站在那儿别动
Just don't move, all right?Stay where you are.
你这个愚蠢的 愚蠢的…
You stupid, stupid
真该把你撕个粉碎
I should rip you limb from limb.
随你怎么做
Take your best shot.
不
No.
我才不会那么做
I don't think so.
让你从痛苦中解脱的
I won't put you out of your misery.
- 是吗？为什么不？- 因为你的痛苦才是好戏
- Yeah?Why not? - Because your misery's the whole point.
看着就很爽
It's too much fun to watch.
你知道你爸爸为你付出了什么
Knowing how your daddy died for you.
他为了救你出卖了自己的灵魂
How he sold his soul.
我是说 那可是挺痛的
I mean, that's gotta hurt.
你心里总是想着他
He's all you ever think about.
你早上醒来 第一个想法就是 我再也忍受不了了
You wake up and your first thought is, "I can't do this anymore."
你痛不欲生
You're all lit up with pain.
我是说 你是那么爱他
I mean, you loved him so much.
而这一切都是你的错
And it's all your fault.
是你搞砸了 迪恩
You blew it, Dean.
- 我本可以把你想要的给你 - 我需要什么？
- I could've given you what you need. - What do I need?
你爸爸
Your father.
我本来可以把他带回来
I could have brought him back.
你亏了
Your loss.
再见 迪恩 祝你健康长寿
See you, Dean.I wish you a nice, long life.
等等
Hold on.
你还能听见它吗？
Do you still hear it?
不
No.
结束了？
Is it over?
它进来了
It's here.
你真幸运 流浪小狗和愁眉苦脸的人是我的软肋
You're lucky I've got a soft spot for lost puppies and long faces.
真不忍心就这样把你丢下
I just can't leave you like this.
何况你并不是为了埃文召唤我
Besides, you didn't call me here to bargain for Evan.
不是真心的
Not really.
你能把我老爸带回来吗？
Can you bring him back?
我老爸？
My dad?
当然可以
Of course I can.
他会跟从前一样
Just as he was.
你爸爸可以好好地活很久
Your dad would live a long, natural life...
就像他应该有的一样
like he was meant to.
- 我发誓 - 那我会怎么样？
- That's a promise. - What about me?
我可以给你10年时间
I could give you 10 years.
和你爸爸一起过幸福长久的10年
Ten long, good years with him.
那简直是一生的时间
That's a lifetime.
你们一家人可以再一次团圆…
The family can be together again.
约翰 迪恩和萨姆
John, Dean, Sammy.
温彻斯特一家又能团圆了
The Winchester boys all reunited.
你瞧 你爸爸本该活着的
Look, your dad's supposed to be alive.
而你本该死掉
You're supposed to be dead.
我们只是校正这一切
This will just set things straight.
让事情回到正轨
Put things back in their natural order.
你还多了十年的时间
And you get 10 extra years on top.
这可是额外的福利
That's a bonus.
你觉得你能…
Do you think you could...
这么简单就能让我相信？
throw in a set of steak knives?
要知道 你这种自作聪明的自卫反应…
You know, this smart ass, self defense mechanism of yours
迪恩？
Dean.
现在你真的被困住了
Now you're really trapped.
- 那会很痛 - 放我出来
- That's gotta hurt. - Let me out now.
没问题 我们只需要先来做个小小的交易
Sure.We just gotta make a little deal here first.
你把你的地狱猎犬叫回来
You call off your hellhound...
解除和埃文的契约
let Evan go.
我就让你走
Then I'll let you go.
我不能解除已经生效的契约
I can't break a binding contract.
不能还是不愿意？
Hm.And by "can't" you mean, "Don't want to"?
最后一次机会
Last chance.
让埃文和他妻子好好的活到暮年
Evan and his wife get to live to a ripe, old age.
嘀嗒… 嘀嗒…
Going, going
- 让我们先谈谈 - 好了 时间到
- Let's talk about this. - Okay.Gone.
别出来 站在圈里面
Stay inside the circle.
快点 迪恩
Come on, Dean.
- 你要干什么？- 哦 只是让你开始一次小小的旅行
- What are you doing? - You're just gonna go on a little trip.
- 下地狱去吧 - 等等 忘了埃文吧 想想你爸爸吧
- Way down south. - Look, forget Evan.Think of your dad.
保护圈破了 快跑
Circle's broken.Come on.
等等
Wait.
- 这是干什么？- 封印契约
- What the hell was that for? - Sealing the deal.
通常在碰到魔鬼的舌头前 我喜欢事先被通知一下
I usually like to be warned before I'm violated with demon tongue.
埃文·哈德森自由了
Evan Hudson is free.
他和他的妻子可以活很长时间
He and his wife will live long lives.
- 我怎么知道你没说谎？- 言出必行
- How do I know you're not lying? - My word is my bond.
- 哦 真的吗？- 在我做交易的时候是的 这是规矩
- Oh, really? - It is when I make a deal.It's the rules.
你已经得到想要的了
You got what you wanted.
现在放我走吧
Now let me go.
你想欺骗我吗？
You're gonna double cross me?
可笑的是 我倒是那个值得信任的
Funny how I'm the trustworthy one.
知道吗
You know...
如果你食言 把我送回地狱
you renege, send me to hell...
我迟早也会爬回来的 而我做的第一件事
sooner or later I'm gonna climb out and skinning Evan Hudson...
就是剥了埃文·哈德森的皮
will be the first thing that I do.
我得说
I gotta tell you.
如果你知道的话 你就不该那样做
You would have never pulled that stunt if you knew.
- 知道什么？- 你父亲的所在
- Knew what? - Where your dad is.
你本该达成那个交易的
You should have made that deal.
你瞧 人们常说起地狱 但它不仅仅是个说法
See, people talk about hell, but it's just a word.
真实的地狱远远超出你们的想象
It doesn't even come close to describing the real thing.
闭上你的嘴 贱人
Shut your mouth, bitch.
如果你能看到你可怜的父亲
If you could see your daddy, hear the sounds he makes...
- 听到他心中的惨叫 - 想让我送你回去吗？
- ...because he can't even scream. - How about I send you back?
什么？
What?
我怎么到了这了？
How did I get here?
魔鬼说的都是谎话 不是吗？也许她在说谎
Demons lie all the time, right?Maybe she was lying.
得了吧 你真那么想吗？
Come on.Is that really what you think?
- 他怎么能那么做？- 他那样做都是为了你
- How could he do it? - He did it for you.
很对 那我要怎么活下去？
Exactly.How am I supposed to live with that?
你知道他的想法吗
You know, the thought of him...
不管他现在身在何处…
wherever he is right now
他一生都在追杀那个黄眼睛的杂种
I mean, he spent his whole life chasing that yellow eyed son of a bitch.
他应该继续战斗
He should have gone out fighting.
那才是他的遗志
That was supposed to be his legacy, you know?
而不是和那个混蛋讨价还价
Not bargaining with the damn thing.
- 不是这样的 - 你知道爸爸一共救过多少人吗？
- Not this. - How many people did Dad save?Total?
- 这不是重点 萨姆 - 就因为爸爸教我们的东西
- That's not the point, Sam. - Evan Hudson is safe...
埃文·哈德森才能得救
because of what dad taught us.
那才是他的遗志 迪恩
That's his legacy, Dean.
现在我们还活着 就应该继续前进
Now we're still here, man.So we gotta keep going.
为了他
For him.
- 迪恩？- 什么事？
- Hey, Dean? - Yeah.
当你困住那个魔鬼时 你不会…
When you were trapping that demon, you weren't
那只是一个陷阱 对吧？
I mean, it was all a trick, right?
你没有想过要真的和她做交易吧？
You never considered actually making that deal, right?
我发誓它不在我身上 它不在我身上
I swear it's not in me.It's not in me.
- 我发誓 - 我们都会死的
- I swear. - We're all gonna die.
- 没有选择的余地 - 住手
- I got no choice. - Stop
迪恩 俗话说好 你不能永远保护你的所爱
Dean, you can't protect your loved ones forever.
把手举到我能看见的地方
Hands where I can see them.
- 魔鬼病毒？- 是的 更像是魔鬼细菌战
- Demonic virus. - More like demonic germ warfare.
我感觉自己像是 《最后一个人》中的查尔登·海斯顿
Like Chuck Heston in The Omega Man.
他们被感染了 我没有 你一直都了解我的
They're infected, not me.You've known me all your life.
- 就让我们走吧 - 我们不能 因为那些东西到处都是
- Please, let's go. - No.Those things are everywhere.
她的血沾到他了 他被感染了
She bled on him.He's got the virus.
我需要全国性的搜索 我要找什么？
I need a nationwide search.What am I looking for?
像我一样的异能者 越多越好
Psychics, like me.As many as possible.
那个黄眼睛的男人… 进入我的梦中
The yellow eyed man comes to me in my dreams...
告诉我去做一些事 一些很棒的事
makes me do things, awful things.
我曾做过一个梦 梦见这人在停车场被刺了
I had this dream where I saw this guy get stabbed in a parking lot.
- 他为我计划好了 - 什么样的计划？
- He has plans for me. - What kind of plans?
昨晚我看见你死了
Last night, I saw you die.
就在老爸死前 他告诉我一些事
Right before Dad died, he told me something.
一些关于你的事
He told me something about you.
迪恩 他告诉你什么了？
Dean, what did he tell you?